

Profile

A software engineer with industry experience building front-ends, APIs, CI/CD, and adept in designing, improving processes, testing, and maintaining software systems.

Currently working mostly with React, Typescript, and GraphQL.

Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Love learning new things and enjoys problem-solving.

Employment History

Software Engineer at Seek, Kuala Lumpur

February 2022 — Present

Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver user-centric features and enhancements aligned with business goals.

Operated in an Agile development setting, engaging in sprint planning, daily stand-ups, and retrospectives for effective project coordination. Additionally, created and maintained thorough technical documentation encompassing code, APIs, system architecture, and decision logs for new features or initiatives

Software Engineer at Food Market Hub, Petaling Jaya

May 2021 — February 2022

Help in developing a forecast system that provides users such as restaurant owners and outlet managers insights and predictions based on historical procurement usage and historical sales data.

Responsibilities include managing and maintaining both the front-end and back-end sides of things.

Software Engineer at ServiceRocket, Kuala Lumpur

October 2020 — April 2021

Continuously maintaining and improving current products to fit the market standards. Responsibilities including attending daily stand-up ritual, contributing improvement to the team processes whenever possible.

Senior Analyst, Full Stack Developer at Avanade, Kuala Lumpur

July 2017 — October 2020

Past Projects @ Avanade

MyExperts (ASP.NET Developer :- July 2017 - January 2018)

Client's digital platform transformation to unite its group and subsidiaries under one system to improve their end – to – end service management;

Details

Petaling Jaya Malaysia +60147201332 mohamad.azriebakri@gmail.com

Links

Personal Website Linkedin Stack Overflow GitHub

Skills

MongoDB

jQuery

Docker

Node.js

HTML & CSS

SQL

Git

React

JavaScript

D3js

Highcharts

GraphQL

TypeScript

AWS Cloud

Languages

English

Bahasa Malaysia

i. e. from order to solutioning, deployment of the qualified resources, project closure and billing.

Responsibilities:

Translated functional team's UX wireframes and mockups into responsive, interactive features using C#, HTML and CSS, built and maintain the SQL query for data manipulation.

Based on the functional documentation given, documented the technical documentation needed for the development of the system and overcoming the potential drawbacks in the requirements and meeting the deliverable in time with quality.

AlphaOil (Front-End Developer :- February 2018 – January 2019)

An upstream analytic's digital program to help increase client's analytical capabilities when performing an offset study by providing historical data of oil wells to optimize well designs, as well to save time and cost.

Responsibilities:

Developed custom charts to visualize complicated data set by using D3.js, at the same time translated design team's UX wireframes and mockups into responsive, interactive features using React, Javascript, HTML, and SCSS.

MPM (Full Stack Developer: - March 2019 - November 2019)

A digital end – to – end dashboard to visualize supply value chain of Malaysia Crude Oil involving upstream, midstream, and downstream businesses.

Responsibilities:

Responsible for developing new modules/features/charts for Alpha Oil System. Also responsible in creating and maintaining REST API to help with front-end visualization and end to end integration with front-end. Tailoring to existing modules enhancement and bug fixing.

Education

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science, Multimedia University, Cyberjaya

June 2012 — June 2016

IT Society - Assisstant Director of Off Campus Division,

Orientation Committees,

Convocation Working Committees - Special Task

Internships

Mobile Developer at Megasap, Petaling Jaya

March 2017 — June 2017

Mainly focus on developing and maintaining mobile application for JobForHire.com job portal at the same time, maintaining and upgrading existing web job portal.

★ Certification

Exam 480: Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3

September 2019 — Present

AZ - 900: Microsoft Azure Fundamental

August 2019 — Present

AZ - 204: Microsoft Azure Developer Associate

July 2020 — Present

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

July 2023 — Present

◄ References

References available upon request